http://www.omsriskandhashramam.org/privacy-policy/

Suggestions For Expunging Items From Your Criminal Record
The Master List Of Hints, Secrets And Tips Regarding Working With Lawyers
Legal Grounds
Ben & Jerry's Ice Cream Not Sourced From 'Happy Cows,' Suit ClaimsNYPD: Sometimes You Have to Hit a Cyclist in Order to Save ThemIowa Man Defends Right to Cuss Out Cops on FacebookNinth Circuit Not Buying 'Bikini Baristas' Freedom of Expression ClaimsAre Offensive Bumper Stickers Illegal?Nope, Parking Cops Can't Chalk Your Tires AnymoreIs Your Uber Driver on the Way Back to Your House to Burgle It?Single Utahans Rejoice! Sex Is Now LegalOpioid Exec Gave Doctor Lap Dance to Promote SalesPound of Meth Found in Apple Store Mystery PackageFlorida Deputy Mails Fake Bomb to Coworker, Evacuates Building, ResignsGo to Jail for Calling Fake Meat 'Meat'?D.C. Marriage Clerk Thought New Mexico ID Was 'Foreign'Our New Favorite DUI Excuse: 'Because the Jets Suck!'Man Sues to Lower Age by 20 Years
Archives
September 2017
August 2017
FindLaw Insider
FindLaw's New 5in5 Podcast: The Five Biggest Legal Cases in Just Five MinutesFindLaw's Top 6 Facebook Posts of the Month: June 2018FindLaw's Top 5 Facebook Posts of the Month: May 2018FindLaw's Top 5 Facebook Posts of the Week: Legal Forms EditionFindLaw's Top 5 Facebook Posts of the Week: Spring Break EditionFindLaw.com Rolls out Modern, Mobile-Friendly RedesignQ and A With George Khoury, FindLaw's New Sr. Writer for Legal Professional BlogsFindLaw Launches New Law Student Newsletter, 'What the L?'FindLaw's Top 5 Tweets From 2016Top 10 FindLaw Articles People Were Reading on Election DayAt FindLaw, Taking Pleasure in the DetailsFindLaw Insiders: Meet Longtime Employee Lorna BeichFindLaw Secures Prestigious Google AdWords Partner DesignationTrust: It's in Our DNA at FindLaw.comFindLaw Insiders: Meet Longtime Employee Andy Zangrilli
Categories
Legal
FindLaw Insider
FindLaw's New 5in5 Podcast: The Five Biggest Legal Cases in Just Five MinutesFindLaw's Top 6 Facebook Posts of the Month: June 2018FindLaw's Top 5 Facebook Posts of the Month: May 2018FindLaw's Top 5 Facebook Posts of the Week: Legal Forms EditionFindLaw's Top 5 Facebook Posts of the Week: Spring Break EditionFindLaw.com Rolls out Modern, Mobile-Friendly RedesignQ and A With George Khoury, FindLaw's New Sr. Writer for Legal Professional BlogsFindLaw Launches New Law Student Newsletter, 'What the L?'FindLaw's Top 5 Tweets From 2016Top 10 FindLaw Articles People Were Reading on Election DayAt FindLaw, Taking Pleasure in the DetailsFindLaw Insiders: Meet Longtime Employee Lorna BeichFindLaw Secures Prestigious Google AdWords Partner DesignationTrust: It's in Our DNA at FindLaw.comFindLaw Insiders: Meet Longtime Employee Andy Zangrilli
Meta
Log in
Entries RSS
Comments RSS
WordPress.org
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy:Om Sri Skandasramam ("Om Sri Skandasramam") operates omsriskandhashramam.org and may operate other websites. It is Om Sri Skandasramam's policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our websites.
Website Visitors
Like most website operators, Om Sri Skandasramam collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Om Sri Skandasramam's purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how Om Sri Skandasramam's visitors use its website. From time to time, Om Sri Skandasramam may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.
Om Sri Skandasramam also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses for logged in users and for users leaving comments on omsriskandhashramam.org blogs/sites. Om Sri Skandasramam only discloses logged in user and commenter IP addresses under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information as described below, except that commenter IP addresses and email addresses are visible and disclosed to the administrators of the blog/site where the comment was left.
Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information
Certain visitors to Om Sri Skandasramam's websites choose to interact with Om Sri Skandasramam in ways that require Om Sri Skandasramam to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that Om Sri Skandasramam gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who sign up
at omsriskandhashramam.org to provide a username and email address. Those who engage in transactions with Om Sri Skandasramam are asked to provide additional information, including as necessary the personal and financial information required to process those transactions. In each case, Om Sri Skandasramam collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor's interaction with Om Sri Skandasramam. Om Sri Skandasramam does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.
Aggregated Statistics
Om Sri Skandasramam may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites. Om Sri Skandasramam may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, Om Sri Skandasramam does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.
Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information
Om Sri Skandasramam discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on Om Sri Skandasramam's behalf or to provide services available at Om Sri Skandasramam's websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using Om Sri Skandasramam's websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. Om Sri Skandasramam will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, Om Sri Skandasramam discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request, or when Om Sri Skandasramam believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of Om Sri Skandasramam, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of an Om Sri Skandasramam website and have supplied your email address, Om Sri Skandasramam may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what's going on with Om Sri Skandasramam and our products.
If you send us a request (for example via email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. Om Sri Skandasramam takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.
Cookies
A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor's computer, and that the visitor's browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Om Sri Skandasramam uses cookies to help Om Sri Skandasramam identify and track visitors, their usage of Om Sri Skandasramam website, and their website access preferences. Om Sri Skandasramam visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using Om Sri Skandasramam's websites, with the drawback that certain features of Om Sri Skandasramam's websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.
Business Transfers
If Om Sri Skandasramam, or substantially all of its assets, were acquired, or in the unlikely event that Om Sri Skandasramam goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of Om Sri Skandasramam may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy.
Ads
Ads appearing on any of our websites may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by Om Sri Skandasramam and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.
Privacy Policy Changes
Although most changes are likely to be minor, Om Sri Skandasramam may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in Om Sri Skandasramam's sole discretion. Om Sri Skandasramam encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. If you have a omsriskandhashramam.org account, you might also receive an alert informing you of these changes. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.
